dilidou.com 2011-12-17

# Privacy Policy

**Your privacy is important to us!**  
We have developed this Policy in order to better protect your privacy and explain to you our online information practices as: how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information.

**Information We Collect**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Izismile.com website.  
Any personal information is requested from visitors that browse our site. The personal information that we collect about the users who have registered and eventually have become our members is the following: name, email, address, ICQ number. All this personal information remains property of the member that submitted this information and is gathered on the SIGN UP pages.

**The Way We Use Information**  
We do not share, sell, give this information to outside parties or use it to advertise third party services.  
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  
We have access to users' emails and IP addresses and may use this information to contact users, to answer the email we receive and for technical purposes.  
Administration may send e-mails to users regarding their activity on the site or informing them about new services.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
The privacy of children is especially important. We never collect, solicit or maintain information at our website from or about persons who is under the age of 13. No part of our website is arranged in a way to attract anyone under 13.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Izismile.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use Google AdSense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://izismile.com/go.php?url=http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**How To Contact Us**  
If you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please send us an email at admin@izismile.com.
